The authority item 2 is invitation by leaking all sense pre-visual church with the name of home and harley. Thank you for being here
for recommending items 6 through 9 from the consent agenda. There are no questions on your own items, and you're paying motion to approve his recommended?
Motion approved! Second please
Go home
Aye
Good bye
You know this new business in New Business anymore
A lot of them is staff reports
The new practice staff available if you have any questions?
Well there's trustee community announcements and the announcements for the team of adjournment
We got most to join me at Shoe.
Second, roll call please
First, first
Second, second
Second
Third
Second, second